the LLM or the agent will run scenarios
in two manners. One with the skill, one
without the skill, just the baseline,
we'll call it. Code got it really well.
You can actually see, I think it was
1.79 times improvement on the baseline.
Were you shocked, surprised at that kind
of number?
>> was. I was skeptical on do I really need
this? We want to give our agents all
these tools. Are they secure? Or are
they exfiltrating data? This stuff can
be really hard to observe when you have
an agent that's going crazy, right? It's
evolved beyond just traditional
software.
>> What advice would you give to our
listeners who, if they wanted to create
a skill from scratch today, how would
you go about it if you were doing that
from scratch today?
>> Yeah.
It's really building it with the model
together. I don't you write the skill.md
myself. Obviously, I don't have time for
that, but also asking the model
um what it thinks, right? Often times, I
don't make the skill first. I'll
basically tell it I want to make a
skill.
And then I'll say, "You're going to do a
dry run with me. We're going to do this
together. And then at the end, you're
going to review everything we just did,
and we're going to make a skill out of
that." And then we also have our first
evaluation from that as well. Right?
It's a real-world scenario of me using
it to do what I want it to do. And so,
like, then I tell the model to build the
skill off of that, and then I adjust and
improve from there. So, that's kind of
my approach right now. Uh I it's very
hands-off, but um
>> I really love that process. And then
evals and things like that, how would
you go about uh running evals? When
would you run evals, I guess, on that
kind of a uh uh skill? How many
iterations would you do before you'd be
happy with a skill that you'd want to
eval?
>> Definitely still figuring that one out,
but I mean, I'm a big proponent of eval,
so I say eval always. But I don't
obviously don't have budget to eval on
every line change. I think
major refactors of the workflow where
I'm changing something in one scenario
that could affect another, I'm not sure,
you know, I run it. But again, it's
really use case specific. I don't have
really general guidance of when I do
that, but I'd say it's kind of like a
If you're doing um semantic versioning,
it'd be like the the middle version
release, right? Yeah, you want to do it
at the at the third at the IO at that
release, you know, the but again, it's
constant performance balance.
>> If you were building a skill, let's say
for a larger team, would you do it a
similar way or what stage would you try
and bring external thoughts in because
you don't want it to necessarily be a
perfect skill for you, but then actually
not great for everyone else.
>> Yeah, I mean, again, it kind of depends.
I like to bring the users out of
consumers in as early as possible, but
that can also be too many opinions too
early, too many chefs kind of problem,
right? And sometimes it works if someone
just hacks it out for a bit,
finds what works and what doesn't and
then kind of
takes the first go at it and shares that
with others, and then you kind of build
from there, but it needs to be easy to
explain how you got to where you are,
and if people don't agree, they can try
something else, but too early might be
not good to have a lot of people, I'd
say.
>> Yeah.
>> Um
>> It could be wasteful of time. So,
potentially two loops, one one where
it's like you learning with the evals,
kind of like refining, refining, but
there's no point refining it too too
much before you get that more external
loop of feedback with the wider team or
even, I guess, you know, extra
agents or extra LLMs to get that extra
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> [music]